<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Chemistry Tech (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.ChemistryTech</packageId>
  <author>BookBurner</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/ChemistryTech</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/WAEzk68.png[/img]
Update of BookBurners mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1596662653

- Included the Cloud Core-mod since it was only used for this mod and a joke mod

[img]https://i.imgur.com/7Gzt3Rg.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/ChemistryTech][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/NOW7jU1.png[/img]
Break anything you don't need into chemical compounds. Can be used as a good form of waste disposal.

Produce Steel, Neutroamine, Uranium and other stuff from chemical compounds.


Contains:
- chemical power plant produces power from chemical compounds
- chemical synthesizer dissolves stuff into chemical compounds and allows producing useful resources
- chemical launcher, weapon which causes chemical burns
- high tech assault rifle, long to medium range high precission rifle firing nanocomposite projectiles
- chemical compound post-processing into ionic particle mass
- production of synthread, hyperweave and three new fabrics from ionic particle mass (one of the pictures shows the differences)
- chemical gases
- chemical defensive structures and chemical weapons

Edit: some recipes fixed, fabrics fixed

My other stuff
Electric fence: http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1103101448
Dickbutt mod: https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1128770769


Disclaimer
Might go through save breaking changes during development, hopefully not :)

UPDATES
- now with something little extra for colonists digesting food ;)
- valves replaced by IEDs
- bulk chemical creation for 50 chamicals at once

[img]https://i.imgur.com/Rs6T6cr.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]
</description>
</ModMetaData>
